<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="200dp"
        android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:background="@drawable/chitkara" />

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/logo"
        android:layout_width="90dp"
        android:layout_height="50dp"
        android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"
        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
        android:layout_below="@+id/imageView"
        android:background="@drawable/logo" />


    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_below="@+id/imageView"
        android:layout_marginLeft="70dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
        android:text="Chitkara University"
        android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceLarge">

    </TextView>


    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView"
        android:layout_width="260dp"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_alignLeft="@+id/textView"
        android:layout_alignStart="@+id/textView"
        android:layout_below="@+id/textView"
        android:layout_marginLeft="-15dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
        android:fillViewport="true"
        android:textAlignment="center">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textView2"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_below="@+id/logo"
            android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
            android:allowUndo="false"
            android:text="In October 2007, Government of Himachal Pradesh issued a Letter of Intent to the Chitkara Educational Trust for the establishment of Chitkara University. The Legislature of Himachal Pradesh passed the Chitkara University (Establishment and Regulation) Act (Act No. 2 of 2009) and Chitkara University had started its operations from Academic Year 2008-09. Based in Himachal, Chitkara University has grown tremendously during the last few years and is fast moving towards attaining leadership position in North India, which speaks volumes about our enduring commitment, outstanding faculty and rich learning environment. The ambition of our founders is seeing fruition as all the constituent colleges are making a positive contribution to the development of individuals, institutions and societies facing the challenges of change.  Among our talented faculty, you’ll meet academic scholars, experts who advise top Indian corporations, the authors of important texts in technology and business and faculty who develop fresh approaches in information management, human resources, and many other fields. With serious students and talented teachers, you’ll become partners in pursuit of purposeful learning and experience.  Chitkara University, Himachal Pradesh have been in the forefront of developing great industry-academia interface and have successfully achieved 100% campus recruitment across major companies in respective sectors. In addition, the Industry reposed faith in the academic standards of the University and companies like nVIDIA, one of the leading companies in the parallel computing space, has granted the status of “CUDA teaching Centre” to Chitkara University. Marquee companies such as ARM, Cadence and NXP Semiconductors are supporting us in terms of supplying state-of-the-art equipment for best hands-on classroom training. Infosys Campus Connect and Wipro 10X Mission have provided us an important framework for our engineering curriculum. We have forged strong linkages with industry leaders such as CISCO, Ericsson, Dassault Systems, National Instruments and Oracle to develop and deploy industry-relevant curricula on various technologies for our engineering curriculum."
            android:textSize="16dp" />
    </ScrollView>


</RelativeLayout>